There's a pretty cool story behind this
beat. [music]
>> Do you know the original beat of Potato
Salad where what he's rapping on?
>> No.
>> Maybe you'll know it if I play it.
[music]
>> Monica produced by Kanye West and Missy
Elliot. Like come on. So the original
sample is called It's a Terrible Thing
to Waste Your Love by The Masquerades.
[music]
Kanye grabbed this originally for his
own song called Apologize. It's early
2000s. It was a B-side that didn't make
the college dropout.
>> It must be [music] more good women than
men percentage wise. So having a husband
just minimize. [music]
That's why a lot of girls cla
>> I forgot this song exist. Prime Kanye.
Jeez, it's so good. But before Tyler
gets his hands on it, uh it goes through
a number of artists. So Ray J sung on
this beat. Good, [music] good,
good.
>> JCole raps on Knockk Knockock on his
mixtape The warm-up from 2009.
>> Sometimes [music] play the villain,
sometimes play the hero. Sometimes I
beer, sometimes
>> also Slim Thug. Shout out to Slim Slim
Thug.
>> He raps on this sample. [music]
>> Cruising a long way from Houston.
[singing]
>> Tyler gets on it with potato salad. You
could press the next [music]
triangle your nose.
Try to mess with my
>> Who has the better verse, Tyler or ASAP?
>> Yeah, that's hard. I think it's Tyler.
>> ASAP Rocky sounds so cool though. But
they're both really good.
>> I like Tyler's raps better. To your
point, I think ASAP has a more classic
rap voice that fits the sample better.
>> Yeah. [music]
for me and them hoes are like divas.